Ever since I won the catwalk competition last time,
منذ أن فزت في مسابقة المنصة آخر مرة ،
now,
الآن،
Every garment shop
كل محل ملابس
sells the same dresses as us,
تبيع نفس الفساتين لدينا ،
It's even cheaper.
حتى أنها أرخص.
What should we do?
ماذا علينا ان نفعل؟
Oh,
أوه،
and the monthly dividend promised to the former wife of shop-owner.
والأرباح الشهرية الموعودة للزوجة السابقة لصاحب المحل.
We still have a long way to go.
ما زال لدينا طريق طويل لنذهب.
Hey,
يا،
I don't think
لا اعتقد
you're in a hurry,
انت في عجلة من امرنا
What happens when something gets popular?
ماذا يحدث عندما يصبح شيء شائعًا؟
Counterfeit versions will naturally emerge one after another.
ستظهر الإصدارات المزيفة بشكل طبيعي واحدة تلو الأخرى.
This is an inevitable rule.
هذه قاعدة حتمية.
unless
ما لم
There's copyright protection,
هناك حماية حقوق التأليف والنشر ،
otherwise there's nothing we can do.
وإلا فلا يوجد شيء يمكننا القيام به.
Copyright protection.
حماية حقوق التأليف والنشر.
Copyright protection,
حماية حقوق التأليف والنشر ،
to put it simply,
ببساطة ،
It's your own original stuff.
إنها الأشياء الأصلية الخاصة بك.
If someone plagiarizes it,
إذا سرقها شخص ما ،
they can report it to the government.
يمكنهم الإبلاغ عنها إلى الحكومة.
That's a good idea.
إنها فكرةجيدة.
Miss,
يفتقد،
what should we do now?
ماذا يجب أن نفعل الآن؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I already have a plan.
لدي بالفعل خطة.
In order to save the hearts of customers,
من أجل إنقاذ قلوب العملاء ،
we launched exclusive customization,
أطلقنا التخصيص الحصري ،
Provide exclusive service,
تقديم خدمة حصرية ،
and create a limited edition of this one for individuals.
وإنشاء إصدار محدود من هذا الإصدار للأفراد.
After all, no one wants to bump into someone else's shirt.
بعد كل شيء ، لا أحد يريد أن يصطدم بقميص شخص آخر.
The first step is to distinguish exclusive services
الخطوة الأولى هي تمييز الخدمات الحصرية
from ordinary consumption,
من الاستهلاك العادي ،
We have to launch a lot of membership activities,
علينا إطلاق الكثير من أنشطة العضوية ،
like,
مثل،
We'll hold sweepstakes,
سنجري اليانصيب ،
buy clothes and bags, and so on.
شراء الملابس والحقائب ، وما إلى ذلك.
So that customers can really
حتى يتمكن العملاء حقًا
enjoy the discount on the purchase.
استمتع بخصم الشراء.
The second step is exclusive customization,
الخطوة الثانية هي التخصيص الحصري ،
which will make it more fit
مما يجعلها أكثر ملاءمة
and fit.
وصالح.
It makes every piece of clothing unique.
يجعل كل قطعة ملابس فريدة من نوعها.
It also makes everyone who puts on clothes,
كما أنه يجعل كل من يرتدي الملابس ،
unique.
فريدة من نوعها.
Thereby avoiding
تجنب بذلك
low-price plagiarism of other ready-to-wear shops,
الانتحال منخفض الثمن من متاجر الملابس الجاهزة الأخرى ،
The third step
الخطوة الثالثة
is to continuously introduce
هو تقديم باستمرار
limited-edition new products in the future,
إصدار محدود من المنتجات الجديدة في المستقبل ،
to hold fashion shows,
لعروض الأزياء ،
to create a brand-name effect,
لخلق تأثير اسم العلامة التجارية ،
VIP service
خدمة كبار الشخصيات
not only demonstrates the identity and status of customers,
لا يوضح فقط هوية ومكانة العملاء ،
It also satisfies the customer's superiority in consumption.
كما أنه يرضي تفوق العميل في الاستهلاك.
Thereby cultivating the customer's consumption loyalty.
مما يؤدي إلى تنمية الولاء الاستهلاكي للعميل.
To achieve stable store revenue,
لتحقيق عائد متجر ثابت ،
I believe that as long as we can do this,
أعتقد أنه طالما يمكننا القيام بذلك ،
The business of the store will get better and better.
سيصبح عمل المتجر أفضل وأفضل.
I want this too.
أريد هذا أيضا.
I'll take one of these, too.
سآخذ واحدة من هؤلاء أيضًا.
It's beautiful.
جميل.
Su Jinxia,
سو جينشيا ،
how many surprises can you bring me?
كم عدد المفاجآت التي يمكنك أن تجلبها لي؟
It suits your skin color very well.
يناسب لون بشرتك جيدًا.
Take a closer look.
ألق نظرة فاحصة.
This way, please.
من هنا لو سمحت.
Miss,
يفتقد،
this way. Welcome next time.
من هنا.  مرحبًا بك في المرة القادمة.
This is designed by our boss himself.
تم تصميم هذا من قبل رئيسنا نفسه.
Isn't it beautiful?
أليست جميلة؟
The business across the street is so good,
العمل عبر الشارع جيد جدًا ،
we have to do something about it.
علينا أن نفعل شيئًا حيال ذلك.
Come again next time.
تعال مرة أخرى في المرة القادمة.
What do you think of this style?
ما رأيك في هذا النمط؟
This way, please.
من هنا لو سمحت.
Welcome.
أهلا بك.
Do you like it?
هل أحببت ذلك؟
This fabric is very good,
هذا النسيج جيد جدا
Boss,
رئيس،
I've come up with an idea.
خطرت لي فكرة.
Hello. Please come in.
مرحبًا.  تفضل بالدخول.
Go now.
اذهب الآن.
Okay.
تمام.
Boss,
رئيس،
just take a good look.
فقط الق نظرة جيدة.
I didn't expect that
لم أتوقع ذلك
you would listen to the murder
سوف تستمع إلى جريمة القتل
because you wanted to hide your identity,
لأنك أردت إخفاء هويتك
I can't recognize you with the Holy Lord.
لا أستطيع التعرف عليك مع الرب المقدس.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
أرجوك سامحني يا صاحب الجلالة.